<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Codepen on Stripe subscription payments with No Code</title><link>https://www.pricewell.io/tags/codepen/</link><description>Recent content in Codepen on Stripe subscription payments with No Code</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 01:45:44 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pricewell.io/tags/codepen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>pricing table template codepen</title><link>https://www.pricewell.io/blog/pricing-table-template-codepen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 01:45:44 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.io/blog/pricing-table-template-codepen/</guid><description>Are you looking for a pricing page template? Pricing Page Templates on ThemeForest are great but they often don&amp;rsquo;t work (you can&amp;rsquo;t actually collect credit card payments). PriceWell is different. Check out of fully-functional example on codepen to see what we mean.</description></item><item><title>How to Create a Pricing Table</title><link>https://www.pricewell.io/blog/how-to-create-a-pricing-table/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 01:45:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.io/blog/how-to-create-a-pricing-table/</guid><description>Pricing Tables are a vital part of your business. If you get your pricing wrong, you could be leaving a lot of money on the table. In the early stages of your business you&amp;rsquo;ll want to experiment with your pricing regularly. That&amp;rsquo;s why it&amp;rsquo;s important to create a Pricing Table that you can update quickly. When it comes to building your own pricing table, you have a few options:
HTML (~ 4 hours) WordPress (~ 1 hour) Webflow (~ 1 hour) PriceWell (~ 15 minutes) How to Create a Pricing Table with HTML First you are going to decide whether you want to use a CSS framework like Bootstrap or Tailwind (maybe your website is built with something already).</description></item><item><title>Pricing Page Design CodePen</title><link>https://www.pricewell.io/blog/pricing-page-design-codepen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 01:42:35 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.io/blog/pricing-page-design-codepen/</guid><description>Are you looking for a pricing page design? CodePen is great for finding good looking designs. But often they aren&amp;rsquo;t fully functional. We&amp;rsquo;ve put together a working CodePen showing of PriceWell&amp;rsquo;s no-code pricing pages, built on top of Stripe (the worlds favourite payment provider).
Check out our Pricing Page example on CodePen!</description></item></channel></rss>