<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Payments on Stripe subscription payments with No Code</title><link>https://www.pricewell.io/tags/payments/</link><description>Recent content in Payments on Stripe subscription payments with No Code</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 10:00:12 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pricewell.io/tags/payments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Build vs Buy Stripe Subscription Payment</title><link>https://www.pricewell.io/blog/stripe-subscriptions-build-vs-buy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 10:00:12 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.io/blog/stripe-subscriptions-build-vs-buy/</guid><description>Build vs Buy Stripe Subscription Payment Your business is up and running. You have checked almost everything off of your to-do list. But wait… you have to figure out a way to charge customers.
You still haven’t decided what solution you are going for to process your payment.
Are you planning to build it in-house or purchase a subscription with Stripe?
Depending on your business type, one plan will always outweigh the other; however, risks and unforeseeable factors arise after making your decision.</description></item><item><title>SaaS Billing: Build vs Buy</title><link>https://www.pricewell.io/blog/saas-billing-build-vs-buy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 10:24:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.io/blog/saas-billing-build-vs-buy/</guid><description>When it comes to billing for your SaaS product, you have two options: build it yourself or buy an existing solution. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the pros and cons of each option to help you decide which is right for your business.
There are pros and cons to both building a billing system from scratch and buying a pre-made one. It really depends on your specific needs and preferences as to which route you should take.</description></item><item><title>How to accept online payments on your website</title><link>https://www.pricewell.io/blog/2022-05-03-how-to-accept-online-payments-on-your-website/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 10:20:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.io/blog/2022-05-03-how-to-accept-online-payments-on-your-website/</guid><description>Selling your product or services online is a must, even if your primary product or service is purchased in person.There are approximately** 2.14 billion global online shoppers** -¼ of the world’s population-.
If you don’t accept payments online you are definitely leaving money on the table!
Bear in mind that accepting online payments for your goods or services helps you reach a wider audience and keep the customer experience running smoothly.</description></item></channel></rss>