<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PriceWell Blog on Stripe subscription payments with No Code</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in PriceWell Blog on Stripe subscription payments with No Code</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 01:45:10 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pricewell.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Recurring Revenue Business Ideas: A Comprehensive Guide for 2024</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/recurring-revenue-business-ideas-to-start/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 10:24:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/recurring-revenue-business-ideas-to-start/</guid><description>Updated for 2024
In this article, we will provide you with 10 unique recurring revenue ideas that you can start today. We will cover a variety of options that you can explore to generate a steady income stream, including subscription-based models, productized services, and more.
10 Recurring Revenue Models (with ideas below) Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) Membership-based models Subscription boxes SEO services Social media management Virtual assistant services Digital products Affiliate marketing Advertising revenue Consulting services Ideas:</description></item><item><title>A/B Price Testing for SaaS</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/a-b-price-testing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:24:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/a-b-price-testing/</guid><description>How did you decide on your pricing? Did you copy your competitor, pick a random number or just read somewhere that 19, 49, 99 is a good place to start? If you did, you are not alone. Most SaaS companies do the same. But, how do you know what your customers are really willing to pay? Working out what value you customers put on your product is a key part of your pricing strategy.</description></item><item><title>How to calculate growth rate for SaaS</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/saas-growth-rate/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 09:24:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/saas-growth-rate/</guid><description>Understanding the Growth Rate Formula The growth rate formula is a fundamental tool for evaluating the expansion of a SaaS business over a specific period. It provides insights into how quickly a company is growing and serves as a crucial performance indicator for investors, stakeholders, and management.
The growth rate formula is expressed as follows:
Growth Rate = ((Ending Value - Beginning Value) / Beginning Value) * 100 This formula calculates the percentage change between the starting and ending values, representing the growth rate over a particular timeframe.</description></item><item><title>How to Give Access to a Google Spreadsheet: A Step-by-Step Guide</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/give-access-to-google-spreadsheet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 09:24:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/give-access-to-google-spreadsheet/</guid><description>To give someone access to a Google Spreadsheet, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to understand how to manage permissions. There are several different levels of access, including view-only, comment-only, and edit access. You can also choose to share your spreadsheet with specific people or groups, or make it public for anyone to access. Understanding these options is key to managing access to your spreadsheet effectively.
Managing access to your Google Spreadsheet is crucial to ensure that only the right people have access to your data.</description></item><item><title>Selling Spreadsheet Templates</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/selling-spreadsheet-templates/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 09:24:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/selling-spreadsheet-templates/</guid><description>Hey there, folks. Take a seat at the bar and let&amp;rsquo;s have a chat about a clever way to line your pockets - selling spreadsheet templates. Now, you might be thinking, &amp;ldquo;Why on earth would anyone buy a spreadsheet template?&amp;rdquo; Well, let me tell you, my friend, there&amp;rsquo;s a whole world out there of people looking to save time, streamline their work, and keep their sanity intact. And that&amp;rsquo;s where you come in.</description></item><item><title>Sell Google Sheets Templates</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/sell-google-sheets-templates/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 10:24:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/sell-google-sheets-templates/</guid><description>Could you do with a little extra cash around the place? You may not have thought about it, but selling Google Sheets templates can be a great way to do just that. Google Sheets is a powerful spreadsheet application that is part of the Google Suite of office products. It is used by millions of people around the world for a variety of tasks, from creating budgets to recording your snail collection.</description></item><item><title>How Does Stripe Billing Work: A Simple Explanation</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/how-does-stripe-billing-work/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 09:20:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/how-does-stripe-billing-work/</guid><description>Stripe Billing allows you to create and manage subscription plans for your customers. You have the flexibility to define the pricing, billing frequency, and any trial periods associated with your plans. Stripe takes care of the payment processing, ensuring that your customers are billed accurately and securely. With features like proration and metered billing, you can easily handle changes in subscriptions and provide accurate invoices to your customers. Plus, Stripe Billing integrates seamlessly with other Stripe products, such as Connect and Radar, allowing you to build a comprehensive payment system for your business.</description></item><item><title>Recurring Payment: The secret sauce for SaaS Businesses</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/recurring-payment-saas-secret-sauce/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 10:00:12 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/recurring-payment-saas-secret-sauce/</guid><description>In this article we&amp;rsquo;ll cover what recurring payment is and why you should prefer it for your business instead of one time payments or lifetime deals.
Why is a recurring payment A recurring payment is when your business charges a customer for a product or service on a set schedule. For example $10 every month in order to continue using the product. The payment schedule can be anything but weekly, monthly and yearly are most common.</description></item><item><title>How to Accept Visa Payments Online</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/how-to-accept-visa-payments-online/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 10:05:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/how-to-accept-visa-payments-online/</guid><description>Are you an (aspiring) entrepreneur looking to start a business and accept payments online? If so, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to make sure you can accept Visa payments. Visa is one of the most widely used payment methods in the world, so it&amp;rsquo;s essential for your business to accept Visa payments online. In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to accept Visa payments online, even if you&amp;rsquo;re not a technical expert.
Why Accepting Visa Payments Online is Important Before we dive into how to accept Visa payments online, let&amp;rsquo;s discuss why it&amp;rsquo;s important.</description></item><item><title>Stripe login</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/stripe-login/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 17:24:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/stripe-login/</guid><description>Stripe login How do I login to Stripe? You can log in to your Stripe dashboard by visiting:
http://dashboard.stripe.com/login
Which browsers is Stripe compatible with? The Stripe dashboard is compatible with all modern browsers. If you are using an incompatible browser (like Internet Explorer 11) then best thing to do is switch to a modern browser like Chrome, Firefox or Safari. If you are trying to log in to your Stripe account and receive a message similar to&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>How to Build a SaaS Freemium Model using Stripe Billing</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/2022-12-23-how-to-build-a-saas-freemium-model-using-stripe-billing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 13:22:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/2022-12-23-how-to-build-a-saas-freemium-model-using-stripe-billing/</guid><description>This guide explains how to build a fully-functional Freemium SaaS business model with Stripe Billing and PriceWell Whether you are creating a brand new SaaS product or updating the pricing model and/or onboarding process, a basic understanding of the billing flow architecture is necessary.
SaaS Freemium Logic Trying to understand the SaaS Freemium Flow architecture there are 5 distinct steps the user needs to follow. 
Pricing on the Landing Page: Users see the pricing table -with some slick features and some cool design.</description></item><item><title>Build vs Buy Stripe Subscription Payment</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/stripe-subscriptions-build-vs-buy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 10:00:12 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/stripe-subscriptions-build-vs-buy/</guid><description>Build vs Buy Stripe Subscription Payment Your business is up and running. You have checked almost everything off of your to-do list. But wait… you have to figure out a way to charge customers.
You still haven’t decided what solution you are going for to process your payment.
Are you planning to build it in-house or purchase a subscription with Stripe?
Depending on your business type, one plan will always outweigh the other; however, risks and unforeseeable factors arise after making your decision.</description></item><item><title>Credit card declines: What do those codes mean?</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/credit-card-declines-what-do-codes-mean/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 10:04:44 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/credit-card-declines-what-do-codes-mean/</guid><description>First, some basics. Your customer makes a purchase and provides their payment details. When you try to charge their credit card, the payment information goes through what&amp;rsquo;s called a Payment Gateway. The payment gateway passes the information on to the cardholder’s bank who will approve or decline the transaction. If the transaction is approved, the funds are transferred from the cardholder’s account to your Stripe account (minus any applicable fees). If the transaction is declined, no funds are transferred.</description></item><item><title>How to accept online payments on your website</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/2022-05-03-how-to-accept-online-payments-on-your-website/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 10:20:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/2022-05-03-how-to-accept-online-payments-on-your-website/</guid><description>Selling your product or services online is a must, even if your primary product or service is purchased in person. There are approximately 2.14 billion global online shoppers ¼ of the world’s population. If you don’t accept payments online you are definitely leaving money on the table!
Bear in mind that accepting online payments for your goods or services helps you reach a wider audience and keep the customer experience running smoothly.</description></item><item><title>How to Choose the Best Pricing for your SaaS</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/2022-04-16-how-to-choose-the-best-pricing-for-your-saas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 09:56:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/2022-04-16-how-to-choose-the-best-pricing-for-your-saas/</guid><description>SaaS Pricing to Perfection Many people start a software company with clear goals on product development, but with no clear vision on how to do pricing. Admittedly it’s a tedious process, but pricing perfectly (which takes a long time to reach) can supercharge your business. But what is the perfect pricing? Does perfect pricing really exist? And if so, how do you achieve it?
Well that depends on your customers. Knowing exactly what value your customers get from your product and what these benefits are worth to them is essential to your pricing strategy.</description></item><item><title>Microsoft Word Pricing Table Template</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/microsoft-word-pricing-table-template/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 01:45:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/microsoft-word-pricing-table-template/</guid><description>Are you looking for a Microsoft Word pricing table template? You&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place. A pricing table is a great way to show your potential customers the different prices for your products or services. Microsoft Word includes a built-in pricing table template that makes it easy to create and customize your table. In this blog post, we will show you how to use the pricing table template in Microsoft Word.</description></item><item><title>Webflow Stripe Customer Portal</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/webflow-stripe-customer-portal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 13:29:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/webflow-stripe-customer-portal/</guid><description>Integrating Webflow with Stripe can be a pain. You don&amp;rsquo;t have a backend so there&amp;rsquo;s no where to store your customer&amp;rsquo;s details to let them login and access the Stripe Billing Portal. Rejoice, we have the solution. PriceWell&amp;rsquo;s Customer Portal can be embedded directly in Webflow without any code at all. Simply copy our snippet and your Webflow Stripe Customer Portal is up and running.
What&amp;rsquo;s more, the passwordless login (via email) sends your customers a direct link to their Stripe Customer Portal and lets them manage their subscription.</description></item><item><title>SaaS Taxes Guide: Everything you need to know to handle taxes efficiently.</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/saas-tax-stripe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 17:24:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/saas-tax-stripe/</guid><description>Don’t know how to handle SaaS Taxes in your business? Want to learn more?
We got you covered! You only need to follow these 4 steps.
Register for Tax number/ Tax Permit Calculate and Collect Tax Record and Document Sales File Tax Returns How do I handle SaaS taxes for my business? Tax is a question troubling many SaaS founders across the globe and not without a reason.</description></item><item><title>Chargebee vs Stripe</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/chargebee-vs-stripe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 16:04:44 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/chargebee-vs-stripe/</guid><description>Are you considering Chargebee and wondering what the difference is with Stripe Billing? Then you are in the right place.
Chargebee is a subscription billing platform that works with multiple payment providers (Stripe included). Chargebee helps companies manage their subscription payments.
Stripe is the worlds largest payment provider and they have their own subscription billing platform called Stripe Billing. While not as fully featured as Chargebee, Stripe Billing has everything a SaaS business could need to manage their subscription billing.</description></item><item><title>Best Payment Gateways</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/best-payment-gateways/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 13:56:41 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/best-payment-gateways/</guid><description>Best Payment Gateway for SaaS What is the best SaaS Billing system to serve your company’s needs and provide a robust, yet simple integration for your product?
Choosing the best Payment Gateway is definitely not the easiest choice to make! That’s why we decided to provide a cohesive roadmap to navigate you and your company through the individual differences of every major payment gateway out there.
Still looking to understand the basics?</description></item><item><title>Saas Sales Tax</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/saas-sales-tax/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 20:25:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/saas-sales-tax/</guid><description>Is my SaaS revenue taxable? Hint: Yes it is and there are some nasty fines if you get it wrong, read on&amp;hellip;
That&amp;rsquo;s the question every SaaS founder has to grapple with. It&amp;rsquo;s likely you will have to pay tax in the countries of your customers (not the country your business is based in). Oh, and there&amp;rsquo;s some pretty nasty fines if you get it wrong. Sales tax is different around the world but in short you need to consider where your customer is.</description></item><item><title>Building a Saas From Scratch</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/building-a-saas-from-scratch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 20:17:24 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/building-a-saas-from-scratch/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s what you need to build a SaaS from the ground up We&amp;rsquo;ve put together a killer list of tips to make building your SaaS a breeze. We undertook all this time consuming research so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what you are going to need:
A landing page The ability to collect payments User registration and authentication User onboarding Landing page Before you go ahead and build anything else, you are going to need to validate your idea.</description></item><item><title>pricing table template codepen</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/pricing-table-template-codepen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 01:45:44 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/pricing-table-template-codepen/</guid><description>Are you looking for a pricing page template? Pricing Page Templates on ThemeForest are great but they often don&amp;rsquo;t work (you can&amp;rsquo;t actually collect credit card payments). PriceWell is different. Check out of fully-functional example on codepen to see what we mean.</description></item><item><title>How to Create a Pricing Table</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/how-to-create-a-pricing-table/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 01:45:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/how-to-create-a-pricing-table/</guid><description>Pricing Tables are a vital part of your business. If you get your pricing wrong, you could be leaving a lot of money on the table. In the early stages of your business you&amp;rsquo;ll want to experiment with your pricing regularly. That&amp;rsquo;s why it&amp;rsquo;s important to create a Pricing Table that you can update quickly. When it comes to building your own pricing table, you have a few options:
HTML (~ 4 hours) WordPress (~ 1 hour) Webflow (~ 1 hour) PriceWell (~ 15 minutes) How to Create a Pricing Table with HTML First you are going to decide whether you want to use a CSS framework like Bootstrap or Tailwind (maybe your website is built with something already).</description></item><item><title>Pricing Page Design CodePen</title><link>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/pricing-page-design-codepen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 01:42:35 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.com/blog/pricing-page-design-codepen/</guid><description>Are you looking for a pricing page design? CodePen is great for finding good looking designs. But often they aren&amp;rsquo;t fully functional. We&amp;rsquo;ve put together a working CodePen showing of PriceWell&amp;rsquo;s no-code pricing pages, built on top of Stripe (the worlds favourite payment provider). PriceWell is an alternative to Chargify and Chargebee.
Check out our Pricing Page example on CodePen!</description></item></channel></rss>