<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on No-Code pricing pages and payment flow</title><link>https://www.pricewell.io/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on No-Code pricing pages and payment flow</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 10:56:37 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pricewell.io/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create a Pricing Page</title><link>https://www.pricewell.io/docs/create-a-pricing-page/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 10:56:37 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.io/docs/create-a-pricing-page/</guid><description>Create your first Pricing Page First, log in to your PriceWell account. You will be taken to dashboard.
Click &amp;ldquo;create new pricing page&amp;rdquo;. This will take you to the pricing page wizard.
Select your Pricing Plans The first step is to select which plans you want to display on your pricing page. Your test mode products will be pulled automatically from your Stripe account. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry if you don&amp;rsquo;t have any yet, you can click the Create Products button at the bottom of the page to create new Stripe Products.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://www.pricewell.io/docs/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 15:49:13 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.pricewell.io/docs/getting-started/</guid><description>With PriceWell, you can get your subscription billing up and running in minutes. The following quick start guide will help you through the process
Set up Stripe The first step is to create a PriceWell account If you already have a Stripe account, you don&amp;rsquo;t need to do anything special here.
Once you have registered your PriceWell account, you will be asked to connect your Stripe account. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have an account already don&amp;rsquo;t worry, you can create one in the next step.</description></item></channel></rss>